by RentAnAdviser.com
No‚ no‚ no‚ no‚ no no
Light a blunt up with the flame
Put that cocaine on a plate
Molly with the purple rain
′Cause I lost my faith
So I cut away the pain
Got it swimming in my veins
Now my mind is outta place‚ yeah
′Cause I lost my faith
And I feel everything
I feel everything from
my body to my soul
No‚ no
Well‚ I feel everything
When I am coming down is
the most I feel alone
No‚ no
I have been sober for a year‚
now It is time for me
To go back to my old ways‚
don′t you cry for me
Thought I had be a better man‚
but I lied to me and to you
I take half a Xan′ and
I still stay awake
All my demons wanna pull
me to my grave
I choose Vegas if they
offer Heaven′s gate
I tried to love‚ but you
know I had never stay
I had never stay
But if I OD‚ I want you
to OD right beside me
I want you to follow right behind me
I want you to hold me
while I am smiling
While I am dying
And if you know me
When I go missing‚ you know
where to find me
Driving down the boulevard is blinding
Always blinded by the
desert lights and
I am alive when
I feel everything
I feel everything from
my body to my soul
No‚ no
Girl‚ I feel everything
When I am coming down is
the most I feel alone
No‚ no
I lost my faith
I am losing my religion every day
Time hasn′t been kind to me‚ I pray
When I look inside the mirror
and see someone I love
Oh‚ someone I love
Faith
I am losing my religion every day
Time hasn′t been kind to me‚ I pray
When I look inside the mirror
and see someone I love
Oh‚ someone I love
I ended up in the back
of a flashing car
With the city shining on my face
The lights are blinding me again
I ended up in the back
of a flashing car
With the city shining on my face
The lights are blinding me again
I ended up (I ended up)‚ in
the back of a flashing car
(Back of a flashing car)
by RentAnAdviser.com